Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 4 and District 4 Locals, 1935-1991 UE.4.1.4
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 4 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1202
    - Local 1202 Outgoing Correspondence, March 5, 1938-November 7, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Burke to Elinore Herrick Regarding Sperry and National Labor Relations Board, November 8, 1938; 14.
      - Burke to Matles Regarding Sperry and NLRB, November 8, 1938; 15.
      - Burke to Emspak Regarding Local 1202 Dance, March 23, 1939; 16.
      - Burke to Emspak Regarding Local 1202 Tagliabue Contract, April 13, 1939; 17.
      - Burke to Matles Regarding Local 1202 Tagliabue Collective Bargaining and Sperry Organization, April 19, 1939; 18.
      - Burke to Emspak Regarding American Safety Razor Wages and Women, April 21, 1939; 19.
    - Local 1202 Outgoing Correspondence, March 16, 1937-May 13, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Herbert Goldman to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, Factionalism and Southern Organization Campaign, February 28, 1947; 1.
      - Goldman to Fitzgerald Regarding Portable Products and Factionalism, March 19, 1947; 2.
      - Goldman to Fitzgerald Regarding Portable Products and Local 1202 Strike, April 29, 1947; 3.
      - Mel Garabrant to Julius Emspak Regarding Bonding, June 26, 1947; 4.
      - Garabrant to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, July 1, 1947; 5.
      - Garabrant to Emspak Regarding Mailing Lists and Disbanding with Memo, May 13, 1948; 6.
      - John Healey to Gary Waters Regarding Organization, March 16, 1937; 7.
      - Henry Hermann to UE Regarding Employment, May 14, 1937; 8.
      - Larry Kamenoff to Emspak Regarding White Collar Workers and War Labor Board, July 24, 1945; 9.
      - Louis Keller to James Carey Regarding Membership Dues, June 19, 1937; 10.
      - Keller to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, July 8, 1937; 11.
      - John Kromer to Carey Regarding Tagliabue Grievances, Unemployment and Factionalism, January 22, 1940; 12.
      - Kromer to Carey Regarding Factionalism and Seniority, March 18, 1940; 13.
      - Edmund Lampaski to Emspak Regarding Supplies, July 24, 1945; 14.
      - Frank Maggio to Emspak Regarding Local 1202 and Tagliabue Wages and Contracts, March 2, 1940; 15.
      - Maggio to J.B. Steckley Regarding Wages, March 10, 1940; 16.
      - Maggio to James Matles Regarding Supplies, May 12, 1940; 17.
      - Maggio to Emspak Regarding Local 1202 Officers, December 24, 1940; 18.
      - Maggio to Fitzgerald Regarding Local Dance with Tickets, October 26, 1942; 19.
      - Maggio to Emspak Regarding Local Dance with Tickets, October 26, 1942; 20.
      - Maggio to Emspak Regarding Annual Dance with Tickets, July 27, 1943; 21.
      - Maggio to Matles Regarding Local Dance with Tickets, July 27, 1943; 22.
      - Eugene McCarthy to Delatour Regarding Negotiations, April 21, 1943; 23.
      - Edward Perdie to Emspak Regarding Local 1202 Officers, October 17, 1938; 24.
      - John Pollock to Carey Regarding Constitution, May 27, 1937; 25.
      - Pollock to Emspak Regarding Membership Drive and Dues, July 31, 1937; 26.
      - Pollock to Matles Regarding Unemployment and Organization, October 30, 1937; 27.
      - Pollock to Emspak Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 1202 and 1203 and Labor Education, May 25, 1937; 28.
      - Pollock to Carey Regarding Local 1202 Tagliabue Strike, April 25, 1940; 29.
      - Kamenoff to Emspak Regarding Policy, February 5, 1942; 30.
    - Local 1202 Outgoing Correspondence, January 22, 1938-April 1, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Frank Robins to James Carey Regarding Local 1202 Dance, April 18, 1939; 1.
      - Malachy Rooney to Carey Regarding Arbitration, January 22, 1938; 2.
      - Lottie Ropell to UE News Regarding Mailing List, January 16, 1941; 3.
      - Ropell to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 1202 Annual Dance, March 3, 1941; 4.
      - Ropell to Carey Regarding Local 1202 Annual Dance with Tickets, March 3, 1941; 5.
      - Ropell to James Matles Regarding Local 1202 Annual Dance, March 4, 1941; 6.
      - Ropell to UE Regarding Mailing List, March 24-April 19, 1941; 7-8.
      - Ropell to Emspak Regarding Local 1202 Officers, May 28, 1941; 9.
      - Myles Travers to Carey Regarding American Safety Razor Amalgamation of Locals 231 and 1202, November 28, 1939; 10.
      - Travers to Carey Regarding Gem Company Union, December 7, 1939; 11.
      - Travers to Matles Regarding Sperry Wages, December 9, 1939; 12.
      - Travers to UE Regarding Officers, September 5, 1943; 13.
      - Travers to Emspak Regarding 1944 Convention, June 13, 1944; 14.
      - Travers to Emspak Regarding S. Johnson Organization, October 18, 1944; 15.
      - Travers to Emspak Regarding Tagliabue White Collar Workers Organization, February 13-April 1, 1945; 16-17.
      - Thomas Woznick to Emspak Regarding Wages, March 16, 1939; 18.
    - Local 1202 Salary and Expense Letters, May 13-July 28, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Mae Ayello, May 13, 1941; 1.
      - Lottie Ropell, July 28, 1941; 2.
    - Local 1202 Bonding Forms, December 20, 1938-June 4, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Local 1202 Financial Ledger, 1946-1948 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Local 1202 Tagliabue, March-April 1937 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Tagliabue Manufacturing Letter to Louis Keller, April 10, 1937; 1.
      - Elinore Herrick to UE, April 14, 1937; 2.
      - Proposed Contract, March-April 1937; 3-4.
    - Local 1202 United Razor Workers Merger, May 31, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - J.R. Bell to James Carey, May 31, 1939; 1.
      - Bell to Dorothy Docteroff, May 31, 1939; 2.
    - Local 1202 Bonding Case, Albert Olson to Julius Emspak, September 29-November 12, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Local 1202 Firing African Americans, November 20-December 1, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Bradford Robertson Story, November 20, 1942; 1.
      - William Taylor Story, November 23, 1942; 2.
      - John Paradise to J.B. DeMesquita, November 24, 1942; 3.
      - Freedome Landu to Fair Employment Practices Commission, December 1, 1942; 4.
    - Local 1202 Memos, July 8, 1937-May 1, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Memo to John Pollock Regarding Education, July 8, 1937; 1.
      - Tagliabue Women Wage Rates, April 1939; 2.
      - Sperry Gyro Radio Address, May 1, 1939; 3.
    - Local 1202 Newspaper, Shop News, July 3-August 26, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Local 1202 Newspapers, May 1939-April 1943 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Sperry Searchlight, May 1, 1939; 1.
      - Tag Talks, April 1943; 2.
    - Local 1202 Leaflets, March-May 1939 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - "Brotherhood Beccon" Regarding Company Union with May 1, 1939, International Association of Machinists Letter, March 1939; 1.
      - "Election Notice" Regarding Sperry, May 1939; 2.
      - "The Time is Near" Regarding Local 1202 Sperry Collective Bargaining, March 30, 1939; 3.
      - "The Union Way" Regarding Arma Organization, March 30, 1939; 4.
      - "We Support You 100 Percent" Regarding Arma, April 5, 1939; 5.
      - Congress of Industrial Organizations Bumper Sticker, 6.
    - Local 1202 Press Releases, 1937-1942 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Tagliabue Contracts, May 6, 1937; 1.
      - American Saftey Razor Discrimination, 1942; 2.
  - Local 1207
    - Local 1207 Officers Lists, July 30, 1940-July 2, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Local 1207 Incoming Correspondence, April 26, 1938-November 21, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - James Carey to Peter Abbondi Regarding Local Dance, February 29, 1940; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to George Scharmer Regarding Membership, April 26, 1938; 2.
      - Emspak to S. Marino Regarding Enclosed Letter, April 26, 1938; 3.
      - Emspak to Edward Matthews Regarding Convention, September 23, 1938; 4.
      - Emspak to Matthews Regarding Maytag Defense, September 23, 1938; 5.
      - Emspak to Matthews Regarding Wages and Hour Act, December 29, 1938; 6.
      - Emspak to Abbondi Regarding Local 917, May 17, 1939; 7.
      - Emspak to Abbondi Regarding Ticket Bill, May 19, 1939; 8.
      - Emspak to Andre Pastor Regarding WIlliam Floeret with Unsigned Letter to Matles, July 26, 1939; 9.
      - Emspak to Matthews Regarding Questionnaire, December 18, 1939; 10.
      - Emspak to Abbondi Regarding Annual Dance, February 29, 1940; 11.
      - Emspak to Abbondi Regarding New Seal, April 2, 1940; 12.
      - Emspak to Matthews Regarding Local 1207 Constitution, December 2, 1940; 13.
      - Emspak to Matthews Regarding Invitation, January 22, 1941; 14.
      - Emspak to Abbondi Regarding Strike Fund, August 7, 1941; 15.
      - Emspak to William Miller Regarding Strike Fund, August 15, 1941; 16.
      - Emspak to Mary Knowles Regarding Mailing List, October 15, 1941; 17.
      - Emspak to Knowles Regarding UE News and Mailing List, November 21, 1941; 18.
    - Local 1207 Incoming Correspondence, March 10, 1938-October 31, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - James Matles to Charles Kaiser Regarding Addresses and Westinghouse Locals, March 10, 1938; 1.
      - Matles to Edward Matthews Regarding Commitee Meeting, September 22, 1938; 2.
      - Matles to W. Sykora Regarding Committee Meeting, September 22, 1938; 3.
      - Matles to Charles Mattews Regarding Employment, November 14, 1938; 4.
      - Matles to Kaiser Regarding Proposed Contract, November 25, 1938; 5.
      - Matles Telegram to Edward Matthews Regarding Westinghouse Committee Meeting, December 29, 1938; 6.
      - Matles Telegram to Kaiser Regarding Bryant Electric, January 31, 1938; 7.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Committee Meeting, March 21, 1939; 8.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Authorization Cards, April 24, 1939; 9.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Floerke Firing, June 20, 1939; 10.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Authorization Cards, June 21, 1939; 11.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Committee Meeting, October 3, 1939; 12.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Meeting, October 6, 1939; 13.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Strike Forms, November 14-28, 1939; 14-15.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Letter, February 21, 1940; 16.
      - Matles to Peter Abbondi Regarding Tickets, March 4, 1940; 17.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Meeting Cancellation, May 29, 1940; 18.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Westinghouse, Women and Wages, June 27, 1940; 19.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Note with Charles Newell Note to Matles Regarding Questionnaire, October 24, 1940; 20.
      - Matles to Abbondi Regarding Employment, October 31, 1940; 21.
    - Local 1207 Incoming Correspondence, April 26, 1941-September 24, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - James Matles to Edward Matthews Regarding Contract with April 18-22, 1941, Matles Telegrams to Matthews Regarding Meetings, April 26, 1941; 1.
      - Matles to Matthews and Peter Abbondi Regarding Westinghouse Negotiations, May 3, 1941; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Matthews Regarding Constitution, May 20, 1941; 3.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Long Island Shops Letter with May 21, 1941, James Garry Letter to Matthews Regarding Shops, May 26, 1941; 4.
      - Matles to Matthews Regarding Strike Forms, June 27-30, 1941; 5-6.
      - Matles to Bill Miller Regarding Strike and UE News, July 2, 1941; 7.
      - Matles to Miller Regarding Election, July 15, 1941; 8.
      - Matles to Miller Regarding Invitation, July 24, 1941; 9.
      - Matles' Secretary to Abbondi Regarding Strike Forms, September 3, 1941; 10.
      - Matles to Miller Regarding Closed Shop with September 29, 1941, Grace Letter to Matles Regarding Strike, October 1, 1941; 11.
      - Matles to Miller Regarding Memorandum, January 15, 1942; 12.
      - Matles to Miller Regarding Check, March 12, 1942; 13.
      - Matles to Al Rosin Regarding Check, March 20, 1942; 14.
      - Matles to Miller Regarding Check, March 21, 1942; 15.
      - Matles to Leo Levine Regarding Check, March 21, 1942; 16.
      - Matles to Rosin Regarding Telephone Bill with Bill, April 28, 1942; 17.
      - Matles to Rosin Regarding Telephone Bill, April 21, 1942; 18.
      - Matles to Abbondi Regarding Telephone Bill, July 9, 1942; 19.
      - Matles to George Kolibash Regarding Back Pay, September 24, 1942; 20.
      - Matles to Abbondi Regarding Back Pay with September 22, 1942, Kolibash Letter to Abbondi Regarding Wages, September 24, 1942; 21.
    - Local 1207 Incoming Correspondence, October 17, 1939-September 20, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - William Mitchell to Edward Matthews Regarding Application, October 17, 1939; 1.
      - J.B. Steckley to Matthews Regarding Wage Rates, October 24, 1939; 2.
      - Steckley to Peter Abbondi Regarding Wage Rates, March 6, 1940; 3.
      - A.N. Townsen to Abbondi Regarding Wage Rates, September 20, 1940; 4.
    - Local 1207 Outgoing Correspondence, July 25, 1937-September 25, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Peter Abbondi to James Carey Regarding Conference, July 25, 1937; 1.
      - Abbondi to James Matles Regarding Conference, October 10, 1938; 2.
      - Abbondi to Julius Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, May 12, 1939; 3.
      - Abbondi to Matles Regarding Agreement, June 22, 1939; 4.
      - Abbondi to Carey Regarding Invitation, February 28, 1940; 5.
      - Abbondi to Matles Regarding Invitation, February 28, 1940; 6.
      - Abbondi to Emspak Regarding Invitation, February 28, 1940; 7.
      - Abbondi to Carey Regarding Invitation, March 7, 1940; 8.
      - Abbondi to General Executive Board Regarding Invitation, March 7, 1940; 9.
      - Abbondi to UE Regarding Rates, October 11, 1940; 10.
      - Abbondi to UE Regarding Members Lists, January 6, 1941; 11.
      - Abbondi to Emspak Regarding Wages and Westinghouse, April 29, 1941; 12.
      - Abbondi to Matles Regarding Wages and Westinghouse, April 29, 1941; 13.
      - Abbondi to Emspak Regarding Resolution with June 26, 1941, Resolution, June 23, 1941; 14.
      - Abbondi to Emspak Regarding Election, August 22, 1941; 15.
      - Abbondi to UE Regarding Contract, October 7, 1941; 16.
      - Abbondi to Matles Regarding Ratified Procedures, February 3, 1942; 17.
      - Abbondi Telegram to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Agreement Changes, February 10, 1942; 18.
      - Abbondi to Matles Regarding Terminations with July 6, 1942, Agreement, July 8, 1942; 19.
      - Abbondi to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Conference and Telegram, August 10, 1942; 20.
      - Abbondi to Matles Regarding Local 1207 Transfers with September 21, 1942, Abbondi Letter to Westinghouse and September 23, 1942, Walter Evans Letter to Reuben S. Dietz, September 25, 1942; 21.
    - Local 1207 Outgoing Correspondence, March 9, 1938-September 22, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - W. Floerke to James Matles Regarding Representatives, February 6, 1939; 1.
      - Charles Kaiser to Matles Regarding Addresses and Westinghouse Chairmen, March 9, 1938; 2.
      - Kaiser Letter Regarding Agreement, December 1, 1938; 3.
      - Kaiser to UE Regarding Bargaining, March 29, 1938; 4.
      - Kaiser to L.D. Canfield Regarding Agreement, December 1, 1938; 5.
      - Mary Knowles to Julius Emspak Regarding Changes in Address and Membership Lists, October 13, 1941; 6.
      - George Kolibash to Sir Regarding Pay Back, September 22, 1942; 7.
      - Edward Matthews to UE Regarding Defense Fund, September 16, 1938; 8.
      - Matthews to Matles Regarding Authorization Cards, August 25, 1939; 9.
      - Matthews Telegram to Matles Regarding Meeting, October 11, 1939; 10.
      - Matthews to UE Regarding Elections, October 11, 1939; 11.
      - Matthews to UE Regarding Letter of Appreciation, December 12, 1939; 12.
      - Matthews to Emspak Regarding Department of Labor, December 15, 1939; 13.
      - Matthews to James Carey Regarding Meeting and Appreciation, February 13, 1940; 14.
      - Matthews to Matles Regarding Meeting, May 16, 1940; 15.
      - Matthews to Matles Regarding Wages, December 9, 1940; 16.
      - Matthews to Emspak Regarding Invitation, January 20, 1941; 17.
      - Matthews to Matles Regarding Information Request, January 20, 1941; 18.
      - Matthews to Emspak Regarding Invitation, February 18, 1941; 19.
      - Matthews to Emspak Regarding New Faction, August 5, 1941; 20.
    - Local 1207 Outgoing Correspondence, April 24, 1938-April 17, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Bill Miller to Julius Emspak Regarding Strike Report, June 28, 1941; 1.
      - Miller to UE Regarding Invitation with Ticket, July 21, 1941; 2.
      - Miller to James Matles Regarding Information Request, July 21, 1941; 3.
      - Miller to Emspak Regarding Strike Report, August 4, 1941; 4.
      - Miller to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, August 8, 1941; 5.
      - Miller to UE Regarding Contract, August 27, 1941; 6.
      - Miller to UE Regarding Strike Information, September 2, 1941; 7.
      - Miller to UE Regarding Contract, September 22, 1941; 8.
      - Miller to Matles Regarding Memorandum Request, January 20, 1942; 9.
      - Miller to Emspak Regarding Officers and Executive Board Members List with List, January 27, 1942; 10.
      - Miller to Matles Regarding Shop Organization with Message, March 9, 1942; 11.
      - Miller to Matles Regarding Expense Checks, March 17, 1942; 12.
      - Miller to Matles Regarding Negotiations, March 20, 1942; 13.
      - Andre Pastor to Emspak Regarding Charges, July 24, 1939; 14.
      - Pastor Telegram to Matles Regarding Agreement, July 30, 1942; 15.
      - Al Rosin to Matles Regarding Telephone Bill, April 17, 1942; 16.
      - Rosin to Matles Regarding Expenses, March 16, 1942; 17.
      - George Scharmer to UE Regarding Union Transfers, April 24, 1938; 18.
      - William Sykora to UE Regarding Motion, August 28, 1941; 19.
    - Local 1207 Salary and Expense Letters, Harold Brickwell, February 18-December 1, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Local 1207 Finances, July 11, 1938-August 14, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Surety Letter, July 11, 1938; 1.
      - Stamp Letter, August 14, 1939; 2.
    - Local 1207 Wages, October 1939-January 1940 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - James Lustig to J. Steckley, October 20, 1939; 1.
      - Negotiating Committee, 1939; 2.
      - Results of Rates Negotiations, October 1939-January 1940; 3.
    - Local 1207 Telephone Bill, April 23-24, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Ray Memo to James Matles, April 23, 1942; 1.
      - Ray Memo to Nat, April 24, 1942; 2.
    - Local 1207 Correspondence, Agreement and Rating Sheet, June 3, 1940-Februray 9, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Patient Agreement, June 3, 1940; 1.
      - P.D. Caufield to Westinghouse Employees Regarding National Labor Relations Board, February 6, 1941; 2.
      - Walter Evans to Edward Matthews Regarding Plant Closure with February 6, 1942, W.G. Marshall Statement, February 9, 1942; 3.
      - Memo Regarding Strike Fund, 4.
      - Labor Grade Rating Sheet, 5.
  - Local 1210
    - Local 1210 Officers Lists, April 4-June 4, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Local 1210 Incoming Correspondence, May 27, 1936-June 5, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Warren Billings to Friend Regarding Appreciation Letter, May 26, 1942; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Joseph Dermody Regarding Organization, September 1, 1936; 2.
      - Emspak to Edmund Churchill Regarding Organization, March 30-April 10, 1937; 3-4.
      - Emspak to Dermody Regarding Organization, August 30, 1937; 5.
      - Emspak to Dermody Regarding National Conference, August 17, 1938; 6.
      - Emspak to Dermody Regarding Western Electric Meeting, January 23, 1939; 7.
      - Emspak to Dermody Regarding Western Electric Report, February 16, 1939; 8.
      - Emspak to William Lyons Regarding New Seal, March 15, 1939; 9.
      - Emspak to Charles A. Globe Regarding Dues Stamp, August 28, 1939; 10.
      - Emspak to W.A. Kirsch Regarding Ad Subscription with Advertisment Application, March 26, 1940; 11.
      - Emspak to J. O'Shea Regarding Debt Payment, September 24, 1940; 12.
      - Emspak to O'Shea Regarding Mailing List, October 19-November 8, 1940; 13-14.
      - Emspak to Lyons Regarding Bell Lab Organization, September 17, 1941; 15.
      - F.D. Leamer to Dermody Regarding Meeting, March 27-April 23, 1936; 16-17.
      - Leamer to Dermody Regarding Meeting Report, April 27, 1936; 18.
      - James Matles to Dermody Regarding Committee, January 4, 1939; 19.
      - Matles to Kirsch Regarding Appreciation Letter, August 17, 1939; 20.
      - Matles to Dermody Regarding Field Examiner Schatzow Letter, December 20, 1939; 21.
      - Matles to Dermody Regarding Cards, November 29, 1939; 22.
      - J.B. Steckley to Dermody Regarding Rates with May 17, 1939, Charles Newell Letter to Steckley, May 23, 1939; 23.
      - Gustave Strebel to UE Regarding Convention with Applicattion, Monthly Report Form and Convention Delegates, May 12, 1942; 24.
      - Strebel to UE Regarding Convention Notes, June 5, 1942; 25.
    - Local 1210 Outgoing Correspondence, March 22, 1937-September 3, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Edmund Churchill to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, March 22, 1937; 1.
      - Churchill to James Carey Regarding Organization, March 25, 1937; 2.
      - Joseph Dermody to Emspak Regarding Organization with Draft Leaflet, April 2, 1937; 3.
      - Dermody to Emspak Regarding Organization, April 4, 1937; 4.
      - Dermody to Tom Wright Regarding People's Press, Organization and Company Union, April 12, 1937; 5.
      - Dermody to Emspak Regarding Organization, May 16-31, 1937; 6-7.
      - Dermody to Emspak Regarding Organization and Company Union, June 13, 1937; 8.
      - Dermody to Emspak Regarding Organization, February 23, 1938; 9.
      - Local 1210 to O. Buckley Regarding Organization, May 8, 1937; 10.
      - Walter Kirsh to Emspak Regarding Organization with Kirsh Letter to Walter Gifford, May 18, 1939; 11.
      - Kirsh to James Matles Regarding Organization with Kirsh Letter to Aerovox, August 14, 1939; 12.
      - Kirsh to Emspak Regarding Supplies, September 14, 1939; 13.
      - Kirsh to Matles Regarding Organization, November 1, 1939; 14.
      - Kirsh to Emspak Regarding Organization, December 1, 1939; 15.
      - W.J. Lyons to UE Regarding UE Convention, August 7, 1938; 16.
      - Lyons to Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 2, 1939; 17.
      - Lyons to UE Regarding Organization, March 1940; 18.
      - Lyons to Emspak Regarding Organization, September 3, 1941; 19.
    - Local 1210 Bonding Forms, June 10, 1938-March 21, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Local 1210 Company Union, October 29, 1935-January 28, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Minutes, October 29, 1935; 1.
      - Agenda, November 26, 1935; 2.
      - Minutes, January 28, 1936; 3.
    - Local 1210 Company Union, Minutes, February 25-April 28, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Local 1210 Company Union, July 14, 1936-January 26, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - E. Dee to John Lewis, July 14, 1936; 1.
      - Lewis to Dee, July 16, 1936; 2.
      - Agenda, July 22, 1936; 3.
      - Dee to John Brophy, July 29, 1936; 4.
      - Brophy to Dee, July 30, 1936; 5.
      - Brophy to Julius Emspak, July 30, 1936; 6.
      - Telephone Workers Local 401 Chairman to Lewis, August 5, 1936; 7.
      - Joseph Dermody to Emspak, August 31, 1936; 8.
      - Agenda, September 29, 1936; 9.
      - F.B. Jewitt to Lab Members, November 9, 1936; 10.
      - Emspak to Dermody, November 23-December 19, 1936; 11-12.
      - Minutes, December 30, 1936-January 26, 1937; 13-14.
    - Local 1210 Company Union, February 23-March 23, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 44)
      - Minutes, February 23, 1937; 1.
      - District 2 Minutes, March 9, 1937; 2.
      - Minutes, March 23, 1937; 3.
    - Local 1210 Company Union, April 1, 1937-April 28, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 45)
      - Minutes, April 1, 1937; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to F.B. Jewett, April 27, 1937; 2.
      - Jewett to Emspak, April 29, 1937; 3.